<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.1" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.1" modifiedDate="2016-05-21T11:54:56">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Sovereign</title>
    </titles>
    <copyright>© 2012 S. D. G. Publishing (Admin. by Crossroad Distributors Pty. Ltd.)/sixsteps Music (Admin. by Crossroad Distributors Pty. Ltd.)/Sixsteps Songs (Admin. by Crossroad Distributors Pty. Ltd.)/Thankyou Music (Admin. by Crossroad Distributors Pty. Ltd.)/Worship Together Music (Admin. by Crossroad Distributors Pty. Ltd.)/worshiptogether.com songs (Admin. by Crossroad Distributors Pty. Ltd.)/Open Hands Music (Admin. by Essential Music Publishing LLC)/So Essential Tunes (Admin. by Essential Music Publishing LLC)/Atlas Mountain Songs (Admin. by SHOUT! Music Publishing)/Chalk, Martin</copyright>
    <ccliNo>6453309</ccliNo>
    <authors>
      <author>Chris Tomlin</author>
      <author>Jason Ingram</author>
      <author>Jonas Myrin</author>
      <author>Martin Chalk</author>
      <author>Matt Redman</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines break="optional">Sov'reign in the mountain air<br/>Sov'reign on the ocean floor<br/>With me in the calm<br/>With me in the storm</lines>
      <lines>Sov'reign in my greatest joy<br/>Sov'reign in my deepest cry<br/>With me in the dark<br/>With me at the dawn</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>In Your everlasting arms<br/>All the pieces of my life<br/>From beginning to the end I can trust You<br/>In Your never-failing love<br/>You work ev'rything for good<br/>God whatever comes my way I will trust You<br/>(God whatever comes my way I will trust You)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="b1">
      <lines>All my hopes all I need<br/>Held in Your hands<br/>All my life all of me<br/>Held in Your hands<br/>All my fears all my dreams<br/>Held in Your hands</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="e1">
      <lines>God whatever comes my way I will trust You</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
