<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.1" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.1" modifiedDate="2016-05-21T11:57:05">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Victor's Crown</title>
    </titles>
    <copyright>© 2013 EWI (Admin. by Crossroad Distributors Pty. Ltd.)/Integrity Worship Music (Admin. by Crossroad Distributors Pty. Ltd.)/Integrity's Praise! Music (Admin. by Crossroad Distributors Pty. Ltd.)/Sound Of The New Breed (Admin. by Crossroad Distributors Pty. Ltd.)/Worship Together Music (Admin. by Crossroad Distributors Pty. Ltd.)</copyright>
    <ccliNo>6454621</ccliNo>
    <authors>
      <author>Darlene Zschech</author>
      <author>Israel Houghton</author>
      <author>Kari Jobe</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines break="optional">You are always fighting for us<br/>Heaven's angels all around<br/>My delight is found in knowing<br/>That You wear the victor's crown</lines>
      <lines>You're my help and my defender<br/>You're my Saviour and my friend<br/>By Your grace I live and breathe to worship You</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines break="optional">At the mention of Your greatness<br/>In Your Name I will bow down<br/>In Your Presence fear is silent<br/>For You wear the victor's crown</lines>
      <lines>Let Your glory fill this temple<br/>Let Your power overflow<br/>By Your grace I live and breathe to worship You</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>Hallelujah You have overcome<br/>You have overcome<br/>Hallelujah Jesus You have overcome the world</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines break="optional">You are ever interceding<br/>As the lost become the found<br/>You can never be defeated<br/>For You wear the victor's crown</lines>
      <lines>You are Jesus the Messiah<br/>You're the Hope of all the world<br/>By Your grace I live and breathe to worship You</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="b1">
      <lines>Ev'ry high thing must come down<br/>Ev'ry stronghold shall be broken<br/>You wear the victor's crown<br/>You overcome You overcome</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>At the cross the work was finished<br/>You were buried in the ground<br/>But the grave could not contain You<br/>For You wear the victor's crown</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
